(Amy:)FYI, it's another cardigan.
(Bernadette:)Your short, sexed-up guy
kind of sounds like Howard.
(Amy:)Your brainy virgin
kind of sounds like Sheldon.
(Penny:)-Good night.
-Night.
(Mrs Davis:)All right, Dr. Koothrappali,
it's been nice talking to you,
(Mrs Davis:)but I need to go home
and relieve my babysitter.
(Raj:)I can relate to being
a single parent. I have a dog.
(Mrs Davis:)Yeah, it's exactly the same thing.
Good night.
(Howard:)Mrs. Davis...
(Raj:)I, uh... I must confess,
I came here tonight
(Raj:)in a futile attempt
to pick up some lonely post-doc,
(Raj:)but instead I got to connect
with you at a human level.
(Raj:)That's a much better evening.
(Raj:)You're a lovely person.
(Mrs Davis:)-Are you hitting on me?
-No, no, no, that would be crazy!
(Raj:)I mean, if I were hitting on you,
you'd know it
(Raj:)'cause you'd feel uncomfortable
and a little sad for me.